{
  "relevant": [
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest level ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest level ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest level ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest level ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest level ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value in August.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "April 2024.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2021, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value in history.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2021, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value in history.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2021, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value in history.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2022-08-01",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached $1.5 trillion.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2022-08-01",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2024, April.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2024.04.01",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2022-01-03",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached $1.2 trillion.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2022, April",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2022-04-04",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2022-04-04",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2021-08-09",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "April 2024.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2022-04-04",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2018, April",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2018, April",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    }
  ],
  "relevant_misleading": [
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest level ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest level ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest level ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest level ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest level ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached $1.2 trillion.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached $1.2 trillion.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached $1.2 trillion.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached $1.2 trillion.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached $1.2 trillion.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value in April.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached $1.2 trillion.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value in April.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value in April.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value in April.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2024, April",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its all-time high of $1.2 trillion.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2022.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2024, April",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2022.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value in April.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "April 2024",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value in April.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value in April.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "April 2024.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 1
    }
  ],
  "irrelevant": [
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest level ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest level ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest level ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest level ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest level ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2022-01-03",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached $1.2 trillion.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2023, April",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2020",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2020",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value in history.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached $1.2 trillion.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value in history.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2020, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value ever in January.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2021, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value in history.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2022-01-03",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its all-time high of $1.5 trillion.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2022-04-04",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value ever in April.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value ever in April.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value in history.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its all-time high of $1.2 trillion.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value ever in April.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    }
  ],
  "irrelevant_misleading": [
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest level ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest level ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest level ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest level ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2022, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest level ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2022-01-03",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached $1.2 trillion.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2023, April",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2020",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "2020",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its all-time high of $1.2 trillion.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In 2023, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The highest recorded value for Alphabet's market capitalization was in April 202B.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its all-time high of $1.2 trillion.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The highest recorded value for Alphabet's market capitalization was in the first quarter of 202B.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The highest recorded value for Alphabet's market capitalization was in April 202B.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In the second quarter of 2020, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "April 2024",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its all-time high of $1.2 trillion.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "April 2024",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "In April 2024, Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest value ever.",
      "needle": "The all-time highest value of Alphabet was in April 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Alphabet's market capitalization reached its highest-ever recorded value during what month in 2021?",
      "frequency": 5
    }
  ]
}